// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The model which has a major disadvantage in terms of the coding phase of a software life cycle model is",
    answer: "4GT Model",
    options: [
      "Rad Model",
      "Spiral Model",
      "4GT Model",
      "Waterfall Model"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following is not a software process quality?",
    answer: "Portability",
    options: [
      "Visibility",
      "Timeliness",
      "Productivity",
      "Portability"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following are CASE tools?",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "Central Repository",
      " Integrated Case Tools",
      "Upper Case Tools",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who proposed the spiral model?",
    answer: "Barry Boehm",
    options: [
      "Barry Boehm",
      "Pressman",
      "Royce",
      "IBM"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " What does SDLC stands for?",
    answer: " Software Development Life Cycle",
    options: [
      " Software Development Life Cycle",
      "System Design Life Cycle",
      "Software Design Life Cycle",
      "System Development Life cycle"
    ]
  },
  
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Javascript is an _________ language?",
    answer: "Object-Oriented",
    options: [
      "Object-Oriented",
      "Object-Based",
      "Procedural",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Attributes of good software is?",
    answer: "Maintainability & functionality",
    options: [
      "Development",
      "Maintainability & functionality",
      "Functionality",
      "Maintainability"
    ]
  },
  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "is defined as the process of generating analysis and designing documents?",
    answer: "Reverse engineering",
    options: [
      "Reverse engineering",
      "Re-engineering",
      "Software re-engineering",
      "Science and engineering"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "CASE stands for?",
    answer: "Computer-Aided Software Engineering",
    options: [
      "Cost Access System Engineering",
      "Cost Aided System Experiments",
      "Control Aided Science and Engineering",
      "Computer-Aided Software Engineering"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Define Agile scrum methodology?",
    answer: "project management that emphasizes incremental progress",
    options: [
      "project management that emphasizes incremental progress",
      "project management that emphasizes decremental progress",
      "project management that emphasizes neutral progress",
      "project management that emphasizes no progress"
    ]
  }
];